<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
   Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one
   or more contributor license agreements.  See the NOTICE file
   distributed with this work for additional information
   regarding copyright ownership.  The ASF licenses this file
   to you under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the
   "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance
   with the License.  You may obtain a copy of the License at
   
     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
     
   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing,
   software distributed under the License is distributed on an
   "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY
   KIND, either express or implied.  See the License for the
   specific language governing permissions and limitations
   under the License.
-->
<alerts xmlns="http://tuscany.apache.org/samples/alerter" xmlns:tns="http://tuscany.apache.org/samples/alerter" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"><alert sourceid="1" unread="false" id="alert_0"><title>Polymer Vision's Readius rollable display gets face time</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, DisplaysTalk about a long time coming, as what is now Polymer Vision has seemed to finally put all the pieces together and produce an actual working product from the idea envisioned by Philips around two years ago. We knew the spinoff was looking to commercialize the product later this year, but after nearly 24 months of coming up empty, a bit of understandable skepticism begins to seep through. Nevertheless, the firm's rollable, pocket-friendly "Cellular-Book" was out and showing its stuff at 3GSM, proving that there's at least something there to put on store shelves. Although the unit on display was indeed a standalone device -- sporting 16 shades of grey, USB, "10-days" of battery life, 4GB of internal storage, and GPRS, EDGE, and DVB-H connectivity just like we'd heard -- Polymer Vision is actually hoping to integrate its e-paper technology into mobile handset displays in the near future. Sadly, there still didn't seem to be any hints of a release date for the nifty pocket reader, but be sure to click on through for the very long awaited pictures of the Readius in action.[Via Slashdot]Continue reading Polymer Vision's Readius rollable display gets face time Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92945682/</address><date>2007-02-19T15:54:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="false" id="alert_1"><title>Sirius and XM set to merge?</title><summary>Filed under: Portable Audio
Well, we can't exactly say that we didn't see this one coming, but for the deal to actually get inked would indeed be something special. According to the New York Post, Sirius and XM are all set to announce a merger deal after hammering out details all weekend long. Of course, it was noted that the somewhat shaky agreement "could fall apart at any time," and interestingly enough, both companies purportedly spent the majority of their (and their lawyers) time ironing out the good stuff while leaving "regulatory concerns" on the back burner. Unfortunately, those very issues could be insurmountable hurdles, as the typically stubborn FCC certainly has played hard ball with each company before, and having one overriding satellite provider with no competition in sight is ripe for monopoly arguments. Regardless, you won't find us complaining about a little Howard just a few channels down from Oprah, or a dash of MLB just a dozen notches from the NFL, but considering that gaining that oh-so-critical regulatory approval "could take up to 15 months," we wouldn't count on your lineup changing anytime soon no matter what. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92940034/</address><date>2007-02-19T15:24:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="false" id="alert_2"><title>Sony's Cybershot DSC-W80: their latest 7.2 megapixel camera?</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
Out of the gates early for PMA (Photo Marketing Association) 2007, we've got rumors of the latest Sony Cybershot, the DSC-W80. The cam's already made its appearance on a few German and Dutch web sites and certainly makes sense as the successor to the 7.2 megapixel W70 launched at last year's show. However, instead of 8 megapixels like you might expect, we're still talking that same 7.2-megapixel, 1/2.5-inch CCD (which won't help improve the high rates of noise above ISO 200 any), 3x optical zoom, and 2.5-inch LCD. Other than a new ISO 3200 sensitivity and slightly larger chassis -- up from 89 x 57 x 23-mm to 91 x 58 x 23-mm -- there isn't anything new on the surface to report. No one's sayin' but perhaps they've added some optical image stabilization to bring these in-line with most other compact shooters in this range. We've also got rumors of a new Cybershot DSC-W60 and Cybershot DSC-W90 -- both unannounced and both said to work with a new SPK-SA underwater case (pictured after the break). The W80 is expected to hit in April for around  280/$368. As to the rest... well, the PMA show starts March 8th so we'll know soon enough. [Via Let's Go Digital, thanks David]Continue reading Sony's Cybershot DSC-W80: their latest 7.2 megapixel camera? Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92929558/</address><date>2007-02-19T14:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="false" id="alert_3"><title>Gresso's Symphonia MP3 players for the nouveau riche</title><summary>Filed under: Portable AudioHow do you make a splash in the already saturated MP3 player market? Well, there's always limited-edition pink, or how 'bout a $4,000+ luxury player which touts "craftsmanship" (not sound quality or user experience) as its primary forte? Naturally, we're talking about Gresso, the Russian outfit already infamous for their luxury cellphones. Their new Symphonia audio players all measure in at 39 x 39 x 10.5-mm making them just a touch bigger than the iRiver S7 and iPod shuffle. Each features a RAZR-esque laser-etched keypad, built-in FM tuner, and 1GB of flash memory for your MP3, WMA, ASF and OGG files. In fact, the four models only differ in materials which range from ancient hardwoods to 18 carat gold. Expected in Q2 with too-beaucoup pricing in the area of $4,000 to $6,000. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92922919/</address><date>2007-02-19T14:22:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="false" id="alert_4"><title>Earth Trek's USB Tape Dispenser</title><summary>Filed under: Misc. Gadgets, Peripherals
Ours is not to question why, only to accept the inevitable convergence of USB and pretty much everything else within the vicinity of our PCs. Meet the newly announced 4-port USB 2.0 hub and tape dispenser from Hong Kong's Earth Trek. It comes in large and small versions and can naturally be affixed with your very own logo for some good ol' corporate schwag. Sorry, these devices are not USB powered -- but if you're the type who finds it overly taxing to dispense tape, then maybe you should be looking into a bionic suit. "Coming soon" in several color options for an undisclosed price.

[Via Akihabara News] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92922925/</address><date>2007-02-19T14:02:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="false" id="alert_5"><title>The do-it-yourself SSD adapter</title><summary>Filed under: Storage
   If you can't afford the real deal, then prepare to get your jank on with this, the not-so-poor-man's solid state disk. The SDB25SD from GeekStuff4U can host up to 4x SD (not SDHC) cards for a maximum capacity of 8GB. Just slip the four cards into the 2.5-inch sled which then slots-in to any available IDE connector where -- presumably -- the total capacity is presented as a single disk volume... who knows? So how much would you pay for something like this: $50, $40, or maybe $20? Try $258.50 and you have to provide the SD flash. Word to the wise: SSD prices are dropping fast -- you'll pay about the same price for a full 16GB SSD card if you can hold on until June or so.[Via Akihabara News] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92910485/</address><date>2007-02-19T13:32:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_6"><title>Sharp's EM ONE: a dual-sliding Pocket PC with HSDPA and WiFi</title><summary>Filed under: Handhelds, Wireless
Check it W-Zero3, Sharp just one-upped your azz with their new EM ONE handheld. This Windows Mobile 5.0 Pocket PC device brings 3.6Mbps HSDPA and 802.11b/g data to the game along with hot dual-sliding action under that 4.1-inch touch-screen display. Unlike Samsung's F520 dual-slider which combines a QWERTY and numeric keypad for making calls, Sharp's slab is a data-only device so they combine the QWERTY with a side-sliding navigation pad for scooting around the 800 x 480 pixel display. However, Sharp's EM ONE comes heavy on the chub at 140x70x18.9-mm compared to the F520's 105x54x17.4-mm or even Nokia's N800 which is about the same length and width but much thinner at 145x75x12.7-mm. The whole kit comes powered by a Marvell 520MHz PXA270 processor and nVidia GoForce 5500 graphics along with 512MB/128MB flash/SDRAM memory and miniSD expansion. The display boasts a rather anemic 65k color palette (albeit, the same as the N800) for viewing integrated 1-Seg mobile TV and WMV videos with WMA and MP3 audio playback supported by a pair of built-in stereo speakers. Rounding out the specs are Bluetooth 1.2, a 1.3 megapixel CMOS camera, stylus, and a 4-hour battery. On sale in Japan starting March 31st for  95,000 (about $797) without contract or  39,800 ($332) with 2-year commitment.Gallery: Sharp's EM ONE: a dual-sliding PocketPC with HSDPA and WiFi[Via Impress] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92903979/</address><date>2007-02-19T13:02:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="false" id="alert_7"><title>Leaders condemn India train blast</title><summary>India and Pakistan say a train bombing that killed at least 66 people will not disrupt their peace process.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6375749.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T13:27:07</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_8"><title>At least 30 die in Iraq attacks</title><summary>A number of attacks in Iraq leave at least 30 dead, despite a security operation across the country.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6374909.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T16:20:31</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_9"><title>Priest jailed for exorcism death</title><summary>A Romanian priest who caused the death of a nun during an exorcism ritual is jailed for 14 years.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/europe/6376211.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T16:29:36</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_10"><title>Czech-Polish OK for US missiles</title><summary>Czech and Polish leaders back a US plan to install missile defence facilities on their territory.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/europe/6376137.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T15:02:36</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="false" id="alert_11"><title>Mexico holds mine tragedy vigil</title><summary>Mexico marks the anniversary of a blast that killed 65 miners, most of whose bodies have not been found.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6376267.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T15:47:12</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_12"><title>'Anti-terror force' for Somalia</title><summary>Somalia's government sets up a joint police and military unit to counter attacks by suspected Islamists.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6375699.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T12:33:12</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_13"><title>Row threatens Nigerian alliance</title><summary>Two top Nigerian presidential candidates swap insults, casting doubt on the alliance between their two parties.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6376521.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T15:53:07</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_14"><title>Colombian foreign minister quits</title><summary>Colombia's foreign minister resigns after the arrest of her brother on suspicion of links with paramilitary groups.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6376359.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T15:40:03</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_15"><title>Wrangling hits Airbus restructure</title><summary>Airbus shelves a key decision on a major overhaul of the business, amid strife between its European partners.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/business/6375517.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T13:04:02</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_16"><title>Nepal king 'takes responsibility'</title><summary>Nepal's King Gyanendra publicly accepts responsibility for "success and failure" under his period of direct rule.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6375207.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T14:11:40</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_17"><title>More than 20 die in Iraq attacks</title><summary>A number of attacks in Iraq leave more than 20 dead, despite a security operation across the country.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6374909.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T17:05:24</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_18"><title>Sling's upcoming SlingLink Turbo leaked?</title><summary>Filed under: Home Entertainment, Networking
When you're slinging media across the home, there's no such thing as "too much bandwidth," and it looks like Sling Media is beefing up its SlingLink line of home wiring network products with the SlingLink Turbo. The new device ups the bandwidth from 14Mbps to 85Mbps, and while the original SlingLinks were primarily designed for a single Slingbox connection, the Turbo vision should be able to handle more general purpose home media networking tasks. The SlingLink Turbo was spotted by a SlingCommunity member on Amazon.com, with an expected ship date of February 27th 2007 for $149. The device is interoperable with existing PowerLine adapters, and has four Ethernet ports beyond the PowerLine link. As far as rumors go, this one looks pretty legit, but with a February 27th date on the books, we should know exactly how legit before too terribly long.[Thanks TieGuy] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93021486/</address><date>2007-02-19T20:55:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_19"><title>It's official: XM and Sirius plan to tie the knot</title><summary>
   It's been more than two years since we first reported that XM and Sirius were in talks to merge, and although the New York Post may have jumped the gun a bit way back then, it was certainly on the money today, as the two satellite radio pioneers have just issued a joint press release stating their intention to become life partners. In the proposed $13 billion deal -- which they'd like to go down by the end of the year but which still must pass rather daunting regulatory scrutiny and opposition from such heavyweights as the National Association of Broadcasters -- investors would get 4.6 shares of Sirius stock for each share of XM, with current Sirius CEO Mel Karmazin and XM Chairman Gary Parsons retaining those roles, respectively, in the combined entity (whose name has yet to be decided). As you might imagine, the companies are already trying to spin this as a big win for everyone from Martha Stewart on down, arguing that consumers will end up benefiting from more programming choices and better hardware, manufacturers and retailers will see increased sales, and of course shareholders would gain value through the economies of scale and elimination of redundancies realized from a merger. The new pals also took an opportunity to sneak in a mention about the growing number of choices consumers have for receiving audio content, from old school AM/FM to internet radio to the the still-nascent technologies of cellphone streaming and HD radio, clearly hoping to sway public opinion on that whole anti-trust thing. Still, keep in mind that the FCC is gonna be taking a long, hard look at this one -- in fact, current regulations would need to be changed in order for the merger to gain approval -- so don't get your celebratin' started just yet. Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93011139/</address><date>2007-02-19T20:30:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_20"><title>Details emerge on Sony's DSC-W90, W200 digital cameras</title><summary>Filed under: Digital CamerasThe big PMA 07 trade show is still weeks away, but we seem to be already getting a pretty good idea of what Sony will be showing off, first with word of its 7.2 megapixel DSC-W80 getting out earlier today, and now with details on two additional models appearing on SonyCenter.lu's discussion forums before not-so-mysteriously disappearing. Thankfully, good 'ol Google Cache has preserved all the relevant information so you won't have to wait until March to satisfy your curiosity. Apart from the difference in megapixels, with 12 on the W200 and 8 on the W90, the two cameras appear to be virtually identical, each boasting a 3x optical zoom, 2.5-inch LCD, Carl Zeiss Vario-Tessar optics, Sony's trademark SteadyShot and Face Recognition features, ISO settings up to 3200 and, perhaps most notable, HDMI outputs. Unfortunately, there's no pics of either camera, although they'll apparently be similar in design to the W55 (pictured here), only with a "finer," "more beautiful" case. There's also no word on price or availability, although that should be revealed at the official PMA launch next month.[Thanks, Rashid] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93004352/</address><date>2007-02-19T19:48:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_21"><title>What tech would the Presidents rock in 2007?</title><summary>Filed under: Features, Misc. Gadgets
   Sure, Washington had his dentures, Lincoln his ironclads and Jefferson his swivel chair, but what kind of kit would they be messing around with in 2007? In search of answers based on broad and most likely mis-guided and / or offensive stereotypes, we bring you the following list. Feel free to rip it to shreds in the comments, just make sure to keep it patriotic -- Big Brother is watching. Happy Presidents Day!#vistachart { border: 2px solid #333; border-collapse: collapse; } #vistachart td { padding: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc; vertical-align: top; margin: 0; line-height: 1.3em; } #vistachart th { font-weight: bold; text-align: left; padding: 4px; background: #eee; } #vistachart th.mainth { border-bottom: 1px solid #333; font-size: 1.2em; } #vistachart td.red { background-color: #f08c85; } #vistachart td.green { background-color: #b3e2c4; 

    
        
             Washington(rebel)Lincoln(uniter)Jefferson(hipster)Roosevelt(fearless)
        
        
            OS
            Linux (last night's build)
            Mac OS X (with Vista in Parallels and Linux via Boot Camp)
            Mac OS X
            Vista (x64)
        
        
            Computer
            OQO (has an OLPC XO at home)
            MBP
            MacBook
            Toughbook
        
        
            Media player
            Make Daisy
            Sansa
            iPod
            Zune
        
        
            HD format
            HD DVD
            LG BH100 hybrid player
            Blu-ray
            DivX + BitTorrent, dude
        
        
            Carrier
            T-Mobile
            AT T
            T-Mobile
            VoIP over neighborFi
        
        
            Console
            Gamepark GP2X, SNES
            Wii, Xbox 360, PS3
            Wii
            PS3
        
        
            Vehicle
            Homebrew biodiesel
            Prius
            Tesla Roadster
            Segway
        
        
            Phone
            OpenMoko
            8525
            Sidekick 3
            Greenphone
        
    
 Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92998051/</address><date>2007-02-19T19:21:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_22"><title>Solar Technology's Freeloader saps power from USB, the Sun</title><summary>Filed under: Misc. Gadgets, Peripherals
While it won't do your laptop any good, this new Freeloader gig from Solar Technology should be able to provide juice to just about every other gadget in your repertoire. The device contains its own li-ion rechargeable battery, which it can fill up from your laptop or desktop's power via USB, or using its 120mA crystalline solar cells. From there you've got a master cable and eleven adaptors to get the electricity into your phone, camera, PDA, GPS, gaming handheld or DAP. Solar Technology seems to have most of the big brands covered, and claims it can fuel an iPod for 18 hours, a mobile phone for 44 hours, PSP for 2.5 hours and a PDA for 22 hours -- not too shabby for the 6.5 ounce unit. Sure, we've seen plenty of similar chargers before, but the combination of device compatibility and relatively low price ( 30, about $59 US) makes this a decent option for those sun-drenched road warriors out there. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92990699/</address><date>2007-02-19T18:54:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_23"><title>Sony's 1/1.8-inch high-speed CMOS sensor outputs 60fps</title><summary>Filed under: Digital CamerasThankfully, it looks like Sony has come through yet again, and while it wasn't exactly in the timeliest of manners, the high-speed CMOS sensor that it promised would deliver 60fps of video output is finally upon us. The 1/1.8-inch IMX017CQE sensor boasts 6.4-megapixels of resolution and the uncanny ability to "output this resolution at 60 frames per second (a data rate of around 384 megapixels per second)." In layman's terms, this chip has the ability to capture full motion video and grab high-quality stills without dropping a single frame, giving users a seamless transition between the two. Additionally, the 1/1.8-inch size and its ability to deliver 300 frames per second at lower resolutions moves it a bit further from the pack, not to mention the 12-bit A/D converter for each column. No word just yet on when these video-centric chips will hit Sony's CyberShot lineup, but it's an awful lot closer to reality than the last time we caught wind of it. [Warning: PDF read link][Via DPReview] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92983675/</address><date>2007-02-19T18:24:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_24"><title>Is "3X DVD" HD DVD's secret weapon against Blu-ray?</title><summary>Filed under: HDTV  While the Blu-ray camp is busy claiming victory, recently HD DVD supporters seem to be circling the wagons around an old friend, the -- 'til now -- unused 3X DVD technology. HD DVD has always claimed it holds a price advantage over Blu-ray, by way of offering low cost upgrades for existing DVD manufacturing processes. The 3X DVD spec takes that a step further, while it's a part of the HD DVD format and apparently only compatible with HD DVD players, the discs themselves are physically exactly the same as standard red-laser DVDs. Throw in a software upgrade to support high definition content, HD DVD's UDF 2.5 file structure and AACS and you have a way to deliver HDTV content on a 9.4 GB DVD. By using newer encoding technologies like MPEG-4 and VC-1 and/or lowering the resolution to say, 720p, full length movies easily fit on a standard DVD. Eclipse Data Technologies, a supplier of HD DVD mastering equipment just announced it is offering free upgrades to its customers in order to support 3X DVD manufacturing. This was followed today by DCA Inc. announcing it has mastered the first 3X DVD disc, and that several manufacturers are looking at it as a possible low cost path into HD video. 3X DVD's potential to allow for noticeably lower-priced HD content to come to market is definitely there, but it still remains to be seen if this, like combo DVD/HD DVDs and Total Hi-Def discs will find a home and support in the marketplace.  Read - First 3X DVD-ROM Disc Cut with DCA Equipment Read - Eclipse Provides Free HD DVD Upgrade to Replication Facilities Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/92975896/</address><date>2007-02-19T17:54:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_25"><title>Leaders condemn India train blast</title><summary>India and Pakistan say a train bombing that killed at least 66 people will not disrupt their peace process.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6375749.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T18:39:31</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_26"><title>Iran, Russia in nuclear plant row</title><summary>Tehran denies Russian claims it is late on payments for work on a nuclear reactor in southern Iran.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6375477.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T18:33:05</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_27"><title>Colombian foreign minister quits</title><summary>Colombia's foreign minister resigns after the arrest of her brother on suspicion of links with paramilitary groups.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6376359.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T18:39:55</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_28"><title>Five US troops die in Iraq raids</title><summary>Five US soldiers die in two attacks in Iraq on a day violence claims more than 25 lives across the country.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6374909.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T20:24:32</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_29"><title>Iran hangs man for attack on bus</title><summary>Iran executes a man over a bomb attack which killed 11 members of its elite Revolutionary Guards last week.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6377101.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T20:15:50</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_30"><title>Flood aid struggle in Mozambique</title><summary>Mozambique says it has the use of only one UN helicopter to help thousands of people displaced by severe floods.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6377427.stm</address><date>2007-02-19T21:57:46</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_31"><title>Manhunt for train fire suspects</title><summary>Police in India issue sketches of two men they believe got off a train minutes before a deadly bomb attack.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6377471.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T07:32:59</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_32"><title>Miami baby sets premature record</title><summary>A baby believed to have spent the shortest time in her mother's womb is set to leave hospital in the US.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6377639.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T08:14:18</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_33"><title>Nato troops raid Karadzic homes</title><summary>Nato troops in Bosnia search the homes of the children of indicted war criminal Radovan Karadzic.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/europe/6377711.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T08:19:29</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_34"><title>Cheney ready for US-Japan talks</title><summary>US Vice-President Dick Cheney arrives in Tokyo to discuss regional security issues and Iraq.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/asia-pacific/6377649.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T08:25:12</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_35"><title>LG's 17-inch W1PRO EXPRESS DUAL laptop packs DVB-T, Vista</title><summary>Filed under: LaptopsIf you've been eying a Vista-equipped laptop to treat yourself after all that chocolate you dutifully resisted last week, you might as well get a TV tuner built right in. LG Electronics' latest 17-inch behemoth packs a silver / black enclosure, integrated DVB-T tuner, and your choice of Intel Core 2 Duo processors to boot. Under the hood you'll find a WSXGA+ display, support for 5.1 Dolby Digital audio, dual 1.2-watt stereo speakers, ATI's Mobility Radeon X1600 graphics set, Bluetooth 2.0, WiFi, and of course, Windows Vista Home Premium pre-installed. While the W1PRO EXPRESS DUAL isn't exactly the lightest machine out there, it weighs in at a respectable 6.8-pounds and shouldn't make a half bad media-centric portable, but considering the nearly $2,600 pricetag LG has slapped on it, bargain hunters needn't look here long.[Via Gizmag] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93370051/</address><date>2007-02-20T15:38:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_36"><title>GlobalTop intros GPS HUD Speed Meter</title><summary>Filed under: GPS, TransportationIt's practically a foregone conclusion that eying your handy GPS unit a bit too much whilst cruising down the freeway can indeed put you and your fellow motorists in peril, and while robotic turn-by-turn voiceovers do quell the staring fits somewhat, we still tend to rely a tad too much on sheer visuals. GlobalTop is hoping to make the roads a safer place to navigate with its forthcoming GPS HUD Speed Meter, which will supposedly makes its debut at CeBIT. This Bluetooth-enabled device purportedly "displays your speed and other navigational info, like direction, onto your car's windshield," and also enables handsfree communications with your BT-equipped cellphone. Moreover, the speed meter can be setup to alert the driver when exceeding a user-set limit, and while you may not be familiar with the brand, it's reportedly a spinoff of f-tech, which bodes fairly well for us actually seeing this thing beyond the Photoshop stage. As expected, there's no pricing or availability deets surfacing just yet, but all that should change come next month.[Via NaviGadget] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93355876/</address><date>2007-02-20T15:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_37"><title>Cylo's 3style jog wheel / mouse spins it up</title><summary>Filed under: PeripheralsWhile we've seen more than a few folks get a little mod-happy when it comes to crafting their own mousing devices, Cylo Technology is offering up an apparently well thought-out device that should have audio / video editors going wild. If you feel more comfortable spinning a jog wheel than you ever have manually moving a cursor, the "three-dimensional" 3style mouse is right down your alley, as the hybrid input peripheral handles the typical X and Y axes as well as giving users the ability to scroll in any direction with a simple spin. Utilizing a ball bearing pad, the knob can spin freely with just a nudge, and can interpret Z-axis data as well as offering up right-click functionality by squeezing the edges. While some may envision faint similarities to the iMac's hockey puck mouse of days past, this rendition could probably last a bit more than 30 seconds before becoming destined for the trash bin. Nevertheless, the 3style mouse can be used wirelessly as well as in a wired form, and can purportedly work seamlessly with any application that supports a scroll wheel or jog dial, but we'll have to wait until this thing actually hits store shelves before testing out these bold claims ourselves. Click on through for a live demonstration.[Via HackedGadgets]Continue reading Cylo's 3style jog wheel / mouse spins it up Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93350237/</address><date>2007-02-20T14:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_38"><title>Segway's RMP platform for nerdy robots</title><summary>Filed under: Robots, TransportationWhat do you do when your overly hyped Human Transporter skids off the plateau of human interest only to be pummeled by archaic transportation laws? Why, start building mobility solutions for robots, of course. We've already seen a few lazy robots riding Segways around the lab; soon enough, we'll be seeing a lot more what with the Segway RMP (Robotic Mobility Platform) now launched in Japan. The RMP is meant to provide a quick and easy transportation underpinning for new domestic and military robots. RMPs range in price from  6,037,500 to  1,376,550 ($50,000 to about $11,500) and vary by maximum load, speed, size, max angle of climb, and battery capacity. Let the robot crusades begin! Via Robot Watch] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93336617/</address><date>2007-02-20T14:12:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_39"><title>Century's Dolphin waterproof MP3 player</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, Portable Audio
   Wrap an MP3 player in a silicon tube held secure with cable-ties and what do you get? Well, if you're Japan's Century then you've got yourselves a waterproof MP3 player dubbed the Dolphin. Ok, the player does carry an IPX7 Ingress protection rating which means it really is waterproof (not just splash-proof) up to a depth of about 1 meter -- ideal for laps around the Coral Key Park   Marine Preserve. Inside, the Dolphin packs 1GB of flash, USB 2.0, and support for MP3/WMA playback off 8-hour battery. Looks aside, at  12,800 (about $107) -- which includes a pair of unusually decent looking waterproof headphones -- it'll save you a healthy chunk-o-change compared to the $250 waterproof iPod shuffle we showed you last week. [Via Impress] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93336618/</address><date>2007-02-20T13:52:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_40"><title>Sharp's AQUOS R-series of LCDs announced</title><summary>Filed under: Displays, HDTV
Step aside AQOUS D-Series of LCDs, Sharp just unveiled their new flagship R-series of LCD panels for Japan. The new line-up ranges in size from 42- to 65-inches with each packing a 120Hz ASV LCD panel, 3x 1080p HDMI inputs, 1x DVI for that quick all-digital hook-up to your PC, and 2x Firewire for connecting your DV camera and one of Sharp's line-up of hi-def recorders including their new BD-HP1 Blu-ray recorder for on-the-quick dubbing. Just for kicks, Sharp also added their favorite new pet technology, IrSS (AKA, IrSimple) high-speed infrared for throwing up images from like-equipped cellphones and digital cameras. Of course, they also feature dual, integrated analog and digital tuners and 10/100Mbps Ethernet to access Japan's acTVila TV Internet service. The big, bad 65-inch LC-65RX1W (pictured above) mama of the bunch features a 450cd/m2 brightness, 3000:1 contrast ratio, 176-degree angle of visibility, while tipping the scales at 66kg (146-pounds) at just 9.6~12.4-cm (3.78~4.88-inches) thin. It's available March 10th in Japan for  1,000,000 or about $8,361. Expect the rest to hit no later than April with the 57-inch LC-57RX1W demanding  900,000 ($7,524), the 52-inch LC-52RX1W  650,000 ($5,434), the 46-inch LC-46RX1W  550,000 ($4,598), and the 42-inch LC-42RX1W  500,000 ($4,180). [Via Impress] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93330298/</address><date>2007-02-20T13:22:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_41"><title>Sharp's BD-MPC70 Blu-ray theater in a box</title><summary>Filed under: HDTV, Home Entertainment
We already caught their 2.1 channel home theater back at the CEDIA show in September. This time however, Sharp gets official with their new 7.1 Blu-ray in a box home theater kit. The BD-MPC70 pumps 175W across a full 7.1 channels of 8-ohm phallus with playback support for single-layer BD-R/RE media in addition to DVD video, DVD R/RW, DVD-RAM, music CDs, and CD-RW/-R discs. It delivers a 12bit/148.5MHz video DAC and 24bit/192kHz audio DAC with a healthy smattering of the ol' in and outs including 2x digital and 2x analog audio inputs and 1080p video output over HDMI. Available June 25th in Japan for  1,050,000 or about $8,779 whenever these come Stateside. [Via Impress] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93314228/</address><date>2007-02-20T12:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_42"><title>Engadget Exclusive: Sony's 2007 Cybershot lineup</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
   That's right, we've got 'em -- catalog shots for Sony's 2007 Cybershot line-up of digital cameras. Go ahead, check the new T20HDPR, T100, T20, H9, H7, G1 (pictured), W200, and W90 Cybershots -- you won't be sorry. All the new cams bring Sony's Super SteadyShot image stabilization and HD output to the show in addition to a hot mix of features spread out across the line; these include such notables as 802.11b/g WiFi with DLNA support, 2GB on-board memory for music playback, a 3-inch tilt-screen LCD, 3.5-inch (yes, 3.5-inch!) LCD, a couple of 15x optical zooms, face-detection technology, and BIONZ image processing -- good to know. Judging by the pics, we can expect a formal, pre-PMA show announcement from Sony on 27 February. Check the gallery below for all the details.Gallery: Engadget Exclusive: Sony's 2007 Cybershot lineup[Thanks, anonymous tipster] Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93308137/</address><date>2007-02-20T12:07:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_43"><title>Woman plummets onto subway tracks while carelessly texting</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones  Granted, texting just might be bigger than Hollywood these days, but bigger than concern for one's own life? Apparently a Kawanishi woman was taking her well-being for granted during her daily route to work, as she collided with a man in a subway station whilst texting away at 8:30 in the morning. Subsequently, she plummeted a few feet down onto the subway tracks, only to be saved by a station worker who fearlessly hopped down to rescue her SMS-focused mind (and body, too) as the oncoming train screeched to a halt just 20 meters before running her over. Thankfully, the dame suffered just minor injuries in the fall, but an estimated 4,500 employees were blaming her for holding up their progress when clocking in late. Notably, there was no word on whether or not the phone was saved, or more importantly, whether or not the presumably urgent SMS ever got sent -- but considering this is the second case in a matter of days in which a human being nearly lost their life to a cellphone, we beg you: text responsibly, dear friends.[Via TokyoMango] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93274207/</address><date>2007-02-20T10:27:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_44"><title>Iran defiant on nuclear programme</title><summary>Iran's president rejects calls to suspend uranium enrichment, a day before a UN deadline runs out.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6378289.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T15:33:54</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_45"><title>Tobacco firm wins payout appeal</title><summary>The US supreme court throws out a ruling that Philip Morris must pay $79.5m to the widow of a dead smoker.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/business/6379767.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T15:48:25</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_46"><title>New footage of JFK's last moments</title><summary>A previously unreleased film of John F Kennedy's motorcade shows new details of the final moments before his killing.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6378463.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T11:04:18</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_47"><title>Heavy shelling in Somali capital</title><summary>At least 12 people are killed in the heaviest fighting in the Somali capital Mogadishu this year.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6377941.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T13:22:09</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_48"><title>Pakistan FM visits bomb survivors</title><summary>Pakistan's foreign minister, in India for peace talks, visits survivors of an attack on a cross-border train.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6379119.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T14:41:38</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_49"><title>EU reaches emissions cuts deal</title><summary>EU environment ministers agree in principle to cut emissions by 20% by 2020, and seek a global 30% cut.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/europe/6377983.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T13:45:47</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_50"><title>Most premature baby going home</title><summary>A baby believed to have spent the shortest time in her mother's womb is set to leave hospital in the US.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6377639.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T09:48:15</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_51"><title>Experts tackle the devil's tumour</title><summary>Scientists meet to discuss ways of saving the Tasmanian devil, which is being ravaged by an unusual cancer.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/asia-pacific/6378279.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T11:40:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_52"><title>Nato troops raid Karadzic homes</title><summary>Nato troops in Bosnia search the homes of the children of indicted war criminal Radovan Karadzic.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/europe/6377711.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T12:53:35</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_53"><title>Nigerian VP 'cannot be removed'</title><summary>A court rules President Olusegun Obasanjo cannot sack his deputy for joining an opposition party.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6378625.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T11:50:56</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_54"><title>Kenya's 'most wanted' shot dead</title><summary>Police kill a man believed to be behind a string of murders and armed robberies in Nairobi.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6378315.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T11:09:37</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_55"><title>Salvador politicians found dead</title><summary>The bodies of three politicians from El Salvador and their driver are found in a bullet-riddled car in Guatemala.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6378645.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T11:48:56</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_56"><title>Philippines approves terror bill</title><summary>The Philippine Congress passes a controversial anti-terror bill aimed at tackling militants in the south.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/asia-pacific/6374875.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T11:21:43</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_57"><title>Australia pulls plug on old bulbs</title><summary>Australia plans to ditch traditional incandescent filament light bulbs in favour of a greener alternative.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/asia-pacific/6378161.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T10:56:33</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_58"><title>Royal seeks to revive French bid</title><summary>France's Socialist candidate Segolene Royal tries to revive her presidential bid in a televised appearance.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/europe/6377503.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T13:02:05</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_59"><title>Rape claim splits Iraq government</title><summary>Allegations Iraqi police raped a Sunni woman threaten to eclipse the government's new security drive in Baghdad.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6378821.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T13:09:02</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_60"><title>US 'Iran attack plans' revealed</title><summary>US contingency plans for possible air strikes on Iran include most of its military infrastructure, the BBC learns.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6376639.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T10:28:34</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_61"><title>Gunman kills Pakistani minister</title><summary>A Pakistani provincial government minister is shot dead as she prepares to address a political meeting.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6379169.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T14:30:35</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_62"><title>Bird flu outbreak in Pakistan zoo</title><summary>An outbreak of the deadly H5N1 strain of bird flu kills four peacocks and a goose in an Islamabad zoo.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6378045.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T09:34:56</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_63"><title>Canon EOS 40D rumors abound</title><summary>Filed under: Digital CamerasIt all started with an EOS 40D splash page posted (and later pulled) from Canon's official Hong Kong web site. Now the 40D's specs are popping on digicam retail sites all over the Intertubes. Most interesting is the supposed spec sheet posted, pulled, and then extracted from a Belgian site by our tireless Engadget interns; here's what it says: 10.1 megapixel CMOS sensor measuring 22.5 x 15-mm, 5fps burst mode, integrated anti-dust cleaning system, 2.5-inch LCD, and sadly... DIGIC II (not III) image processing. It's that last bit of information which makes us a bit skeptical. Although the DIGIC II can be found in their full-frame 400D, the improved DIGIC III is already loosed thereby bringing the whole spec sheet into question. No worries, if Canon is ready to push the 40D out the door then it'll be soon. The big PMA show kicks off in just a few weeks. Now quit staring at that picture, it's not the 40D.[Via Digital Photography Blog] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93789980/</address><date>2007-02-21T13:17:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_64"><title>Blackberry 8800 now on Cingular</title><summary>Filed under: CellphonesStraighten your ties and button your suit jackets, RIM's promiscuous debutante -- the Blackberry 8800 -- is up and dancin' on on Cingular's website. $500 list, or $300 after $50 mail-in rebate and 2-year contract, the 8800 brings everything we expected: quad-band EDGE, GPS, microSD expansion, Bluetooth 2.0, push-to-talk support, and 5-hours talk / 24-days standby in a 0.55-inch device weighing just 4.73-ounces. 3G data? No. WiFi? Not this time. For that we'll have to hold tight for the anticipated mid-year launch of the 8820. [Thanks, President and everyone who sent this in] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93789982/</address><date>2007-02-21T12:47:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_65"><title>Ubixon's Lubix Bluetooth stereo headsets: the magnets make the magic</title><summary>Filed under: Portable Audio
Here's an interesting twist to the Bluetooth headset from Ubixon -- the UBHS-LC1-3D and UBHS-NC1-3D. These Lubix headsets consist of two, magnetically held halves which can be separated and bunged into the ears or slung around the neck, connected for easy toting. They both simulated 3D sound and Bluetooth 2.0 with support for the A2DP, AVRCP, HSP, and HFP profiles. In other words, they support stereo Bluetooth audio while allowing you to control your like-profiled audio device from up to 10-meters away. They'll even work seamlessly (as seamless as Bluetooth gets anyway) with your cellphone although the LC1 does it a bit better (and bulkier) by flashing the caller's ID on that one-line LCD screen. The 28-gram LC1 delivers 10 hours of talk or 9 hours of music while the NC1 goes 6-hours or 5-hours in a lighter, 22-gram package. The LC1 hits Korea for 79,000KRW ($84) while the NC1 slips in at about 59,000KRW ($63).  [Via AVING] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93781795/</address><date>2007-02-21T11:47:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_66"><title>Cellphone-packing smoke detector dials for danger</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, Misc. GadgetsWhile most smoke detectors will handle the basic job of detecting smoke just fine (providing you check that batt regularly), there's plenty of options out there for those wanting a little something extra, be it added style or additional functionality. Joining those other over-achieving smoke detectors is this new unit from Japanese manufacturer Keisoku Giken, which will automatically phone you at the first whiff of smoke to inform you of its impending demise. Unfortunately, you'll have to supply your own cellphone and service for it (it doesn't appear to support landlines), which makes the device's already hefty 16,800 yen price tag (about $140) even less of a bargain.[Via Textually.org] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93743515/</address><date>2007-02-21T09:24:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_67"><title>TDK's Xa-10 mini flat panel speakers</title><summary>Filed under: Peripherals, Portable Audio
TDK just slipped NXT's crazy-thin SoundVu technology into your pocket. That's right, the 80   117 x 16-mm (3.15 x 4.6 x 0.63-inch) Xa-10 flat panel speaker brings a 1.2W x 2ch waft of breathy bass you might otherwise choose not to float from your trou. The speakers will accept USB power (or batteries) and a mini-stereo input when they hit Japan in March for just  2,980 or about $25.  [Via Impress] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93727030/</address><date>2007-02-21T08:02:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_68"><title>Lexar intros 300x UDMA CompactFlash cards, readers</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras, StorageLexar has already given its SDHC cards a boost this year, and the company doesn't seem to be wasting any time bringing its CompactFlash offerings up to speed as well, today introducing a series of new 300x UDMA CompactFlash cards, as well as a pair of card readers to go along with 'em. Available in 2, 4, and 8GB varities, the cards are said to be 125% faster than the company's current CompactFlash cards, delivering a sustained write time of 45MB per second. To hit that top speed, however, you'll need to use them with a UDMA-enabled device, which are currently a rare breed, although Lexar says it expects "several" UDMA-enabled digital cameras to be announced later this year. In addition those mystery cameras, you'll also be able to get the most out of the cards using one of the two UDMA card readers Lexar's set to release this spring, available in your choice of FireWire or USB 2.0 models for $80 and $50 respectively. The cards themselves should also be released about the same time, although Lexar doesn't seem willing to spill the details on how much they're gonna cost just yet.Read - Photography Blog, Lexar Professional UDMA 300x Memory CardsRead - Photography Blog, Lexar UDMA Card Readers Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93699645/</address><date>2007-02-21T06:31:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_69"><title>Fon wants you to help steal business from Starbucks and T-Mobile</title><summary>Filed under: Wireless, Networking
Oh tricky, sneaky Fon. Fresh off their 10,000 Fonero giveaway, they're stepping up the ante with how they give away their loss-leader routers. Their newest campaign is sure to strike a chord with armchair entrepreneurs and Adbusters fans alike: if you live within the immediate vicinity of a Starbucks (read: WiFi range), Fon would like to send you one of their Foneros. Why? Because, if you recall, when you allow users to connect with your internet connection over your Fonero, Fon splits the profit with you -- $1 for every user (who pays $2 to use your connection). So for every $10 T-Mobile / Starbucks WiFi user you swipe, Fon gives you a buck; now, granted this still isn't a scheme for those paranoid about home network security, bandwidth usage, or nefarious hax0rs type with a spoofed MAC and a keen eye for easy hotspot access, but who knows, for those near Starbucks (yes, they'll be checking against known locations) it might even be worth it to buy a budget DSL line just to profit with Fon. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93662859/</address><date>2007-02-21T05:01:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_70"><title>Vonage to become Vonage Wireless?</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, WirelessVoIP provider Vonage has already cut a deal with EarthLink to resell WiFi, presumably to go along with some sort of WiFi phone service, but could they have something way crazier (and more costly) on tap? BusinessWeek speculates that Vonage might be getting into the cellular game by launching an MVNO (Mobile Virtual Network Operator). It's not hard to imagine them offering something similar to T-Mobile's HotSpot @Home service, which lets you use a WiFi-enabled cellphone to make VoIP calls over WiFi and and then seamlessly switch over to cellular networks whenever you're outside WiFi range. The problem is that launching an MVNO is no small undertaking. ESPN shuttered MobileESPN last year after failing to attract more than a handful of subscribers, and Amp'd and Helio have spent hundreds of millions of dollars to carve out a slice of what is an incredibly competitive wireless market (Apple was working on an MVNO to accompany the launch of the iPhone, but scrapped the whole thing once it became obvious how difficult it would be to gain marketshare). Could they do it? Maybe, but not without spending a TON of money, which is why it's more likely that they'll introduce a more modest Voice over WiFi service.[Via GigaOm] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93658206/</address><date>2007-02-21T04:25:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_71"><title>Desktop Digital Photo Cube shows photos on diminutive LCD</title><summary>Filed under: Displays, Misc. Gadgets
Here's one from the same folks who brought you the USB Sound Flash Drive, and while eNECESSITIES' Desktop Digital Photo Cube may not adorn your wall as fashionably as a digiframe might, this piece is made for conversation. Ready to perch atop your living room table or office desk, the cube sports a squint-inducing 1- x 1-inch color LCD display, power / brightness / skip buttons, USB 2.0 connectivity, and the ability to internally store "up to 30 digital photos" for cycling through on the built-in screen. Additionally, the "mood light" should set the tone for the upcoming photo, and those looking for the ultimate party favor can toss their own logo on here for an additional charge. Unfortunately, we're not quite sure just how this snapshot showin' block gets its juice, but those looking to snag 25 or more (sorry, non-bulk customers) can find out for themselves at $51.34 a pop.[Via Everything USB] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93640955/</address><date>2007-02-21T03:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_72"><title>IEEE pushing 802.16m WiMAX to 1Gbps, hopes to converge with 4G</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, WirelessIf there's one thing that we'll never be satisfied with, it's finding out just how many nanoseconds we can shave off our download times from year to year, and thankfully, the IEEE seems to get that. While it has certainly taken its sweet time with 802.11n, the task force has already voted to make 100G the next Ethernet speed, and now it's pushing to make WiMAX implementations even quicker. Reportedly announced at 3GSM, the IEEE has began working on a new version of the 802.16 standard, dubbed 802.16m, which "could push data transfer speeds up to 1Gbps while maintaining backwards compatibility with existing WiMAX radios." Potentially more interesting than cheering for speed boosts is the group's outright assurance that this protocol will meet the ITU's requirements for 4G, insinuating that it should be the token choice for further 4G developments. Nevertheless, the increased bandwidth is supposedly needed due to convergence between VoIP and various forms of multimedia (IPTV, streaming video, digital downloads, etc.), and however true that may be, some skeptics are still understandably doubting the whole "backwards compatibility" aspect. Still, the IEEE hopes to have this together by "the end of 2009," but considering the team's less-than-stellar track record in the deadline department, we're not holding our collective breath.[Via DailyWireless] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93621068/</address><date>2007-02-21T02:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_73"><title>GPS-enabled wind chimes sound off while geo-tracking</title><summary>Filed under: GPS
If you think the Dandellas were outlandish uses of GPS technology, here's one that comes mighty close to one-upping even those. The GPS-enabled wind chimes have DIY written all over them, and while the chimes themselves where purchased (after a failed attempt at creating his own, notably), basically everything else that makes the system tick was homegrown. Utilizing Mologogo, servos, circuit boards, and a good bit of coding, the GPS chimes emit their music whenever the tracked individual's cellphone moves in a user-selected path, essentially acting as an alert that someone's headed to their domicile. Of course, the actual options here are a tad limited (albeit very intriguing), but the foundation of the project could indeed be used for a much broader geo-tracking scenario. Regardless, we know there are folks out there eager to give this a whirl, and thankfully for you, everything you need to know (including the oh-so-critical code) is just a Read link away.[Via MAKE] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93596281/</address><date>2007-02-21T01:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_74"><title>Sigma finally cops to a release date for its SD14 DSLR</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
Well it'll have been over six months between the time we first heard about it and when it actually hits store shelves, but we finally have a solid release date for the somewhat-anticipated, Foveon-packing Sigma SD14 DSLR. If it's possible for you to remember back that far, you may recall that Sigma attempted to drum up some interest in this 14 megapixel shooter with a teaser campaign in late August of last year, just before it was officially announced at Photokina 2006. The disappointment came a few months later when Sigma pushed back the SD14's street launch to March, citing some hardware issue that the company wouldn't disclose. And according to a press release on Sigma's website, the problem has indeed been addressed, with the camera scheduled to ship starting on the 6th of next month. Keep in mind, though, that this model isn't for the thrifty -- it's gonna cost you over $2,000 to get in on this action. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93572592/</address><date>2007-02-21T00:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_75"><title>Quantum strikes again, charging iPhone touchscreen infringement</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, DisplaysIt's not just Apple's ubiquitous click-wheel that Quantum Research is bothering Apple about these days, Quantum is also fussing about the iPhone's touchscreen technology. "We will be looking very carefully at the iPhone," says Duncan Bryan, licensing director at QR. And wouldn't you know: "The description of the iPhone suggests it uses a rear-surface touch screen, and has proximity sensing which can tell if it is held to the ear. That's a QR capability." No formal lawsuit has been filed yet, but based on Apple's complete denial and counterclaims of QR's December 2005 click-wheel allegations, we're guessing it won't be backing down on this one anytime soon. Apparently this "charge transfer capacitive sensing" stuff has been licensed to Motorola and was invented by QR's founder and CEO Hal Philipp. Usually we'd be content to sit back and watch, but all these Apple-related lawsuits and copycats are getting a little tried -- remember those good old fashioned RIM / NTP days?[Via AppleInsider] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93553936/</address><date>2007-02-20T23:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_76"><title>Motion Computing unveils RFID-reading C5 medical tablet PC</title><summary>Filed under: Tablet PCs, WirelessAlthough we sincerely hope your only encounter with a clinical assistant tablet PC comes by way of your occupation, it looks like Motion Computing is busting out a medically-focused device to help the dear LPNs keep things in order for the high-falutin'  doctors. The C5 touts a vertically centered design, top-mounted carry handle, handwriting recognition, built-in digital camera for documenting wounds, time-stamp / voice-tag capabilities, and even an optional RFID reader to easily check patients in by scanning their wrist straps. Claiming to be the world's first device in the new mobile clinical assistant (MCA) category of PCs, it packs a 1.2GHz Intel Core Solo U1400 processor, Windows Vista Business or Windows XP Tablet PC Edition, a 10.4-inch XGA touchscreen, up to 1.5GB of DDR2 RAM, 30 / 60GB 1.8-inch hard drive options, 802.11a/b/g, Bluetooth, and a rechargeable Li-ion to boot. Furthermore, it weighs in at just 3.1-pounds, so toting this bad boy around the office shouldn't be too much of a burden, and the "durable, semi-sealed enclosure" shouldn't have any issues handling the daily mishaps of your average doctor's lounge. So if you've been looking for a way to digitize your office and get far, far away from those paper-filled drawers, we're sure your IT rep will be hitting you up soon to sneak a peek at this $2,199 tablet.[Via GottaBeMobile] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93548878/</address><date>2007-02-20T23:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_77"><title>Prober P360 GPS / PMP handheld does it all</title><summary>Filed under: GPS
These fanciful all-in-one devices just don't seem to come Europe or North America's way very often, and unfortunately for most, Prober's P360 doesn't seem to be breaking that mold anytime soon. Packing a respectable mix of multimedia and GPS capabilities, this pocket-friendly device packs a 3.5-inch touchscreen display, 400MHz Samsung S3C2440A processor, 64MB of NAND Flash ROM, 64MB of SDRAM, WinCE 4.2 runnin' the show, a SiRF Star III chipset, and a built-in speaker to boot. Furthermore, you'll find a dual-mode map for wrapping your brain around POI locations, voice guidance, a rechargeable five-hour Li-ion battery, SD card slot, USB 1.1, wired remote / headphones, audio out, and the ability to play back WMV, WMA, and WAV files on the AV front, while handling a bevy of snapshot formats and even boasting a text viewer. Unfortunately, we've no idea how much the P360 will run folks who are lucky enough to acquire it in four to six weeks, but just know that most of the world will probably envy you.[Via NaviGadget] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93531504/</address><date>2007-02-20T22:38:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_78"><title>Shredz64 project bringing Guitar Hero to the Commodore 64</title><summary>Filed under: Gaming  We've already seen the Guitar Hero controller hooked up to a PC, but hardware hacker Toni has decided up the difficultly level even further, endeavoring to wire the ubiquitous plastic axe to his Commodore 64, complete with an all new "Guitar Hero-like" C64 game. While he's still quite a ways from fully realizing that goal, as the pic above and audio clip on the page linked below show, he is making considerable progress, with all of the guitar's buttons working, although the whammy bar, sadly, remains silent. Unfortunately, it's also been over a month since the last update on the project, so we can only hope that he hasn't given up on it -- there's undoubtedly countless C64s just waiting to be dusted off as soon as the DIY guide is ready.[Thanks, Joseph S] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93511887/</address><date>2007-02-20T22:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_79"><title>Thrustmaster unveils bevy of Wiimote accessories</title><summary>Filed under: Gaming
If you can't penetrate the market early, you might as well arrive fashionably late with a tempting pricetag, right?. Apparently, Thrustmaster's trying to do just that with its latest barrage of Wiimote accessories, as the firm's charging (and non-charging) docking stations arrive a few months after JoyTech and Nyko's renditions, and the Wiimote sleeves are almost an afterthought at this point. Nevertheless, the T-Charge NW comes in black or white finishes, charges two AA cells via USB (four included), sports a blue status LED, and of course, neatly holds your dear Wiimote / nunchuck combo. The T-Care NW removes the charging functionality, but still manages to include a set of silicone protector sleeves for one Wiimote / nunchuck tandem, and if you're already set in the dock department, the controller covers are available all by their lonesome as well. Thrustmaster's lineup seems to hit all the main areas of concern, including price, as a set of sleeves will run you $9.99 while the T-Care NW and T-Charge NW demand $14.99 and $24.99, respectively. So if you're intrigued about these budget-friendly offerings and just adore high-resolution shots, head on over to Joystiq for a gallery of photos while you wait for these to land in April.[Via Joystiq] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93508830/</address><date>2007-02-20T21:38:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_80"><title>Sony Cybershot G1 digital camera detailed</title><summary>Filed under: Digital CamerasThat batch of new Sony Cybershots let loose this morning was quite a bit to digest all at once, so we thought we'd take a minute to go over one of the more interesting of the still-to-be-officially-announced cameras in greater detail, namely, the Cybershot G1. Apart from that new (for Sony) model name, the camera's particularly notable for its big 3.5-inch (or possibly 3-inch) LCD and uncommonly spacious 2GB of internal memory. Though less unusual, the camera's other specs are also nothing to sneeze at, with a decent 6 megapixel resolution, 3x optical zoom, Carl Zeiss Vario-Tesar lens, built-in WiFi, and Sony's usual SteadyShot and Anti-Blur features. Still not clear, unfortunately, is the price, although as we mentioned earlier, that should be revealed by the end of the month. Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93489405/</address><date>2007-02-20T21:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_81"><title>Magellan preps Maestro 4000, 4040, and 4050 GPS units for release</title><summary>Filed under: GPS
Magellan's been known to toss out GPS units three at a time before, and while the company hasn't come forward yet about its presumably forthcoming trio of navigation devices, we've got the skinny anyway. All three Maestro units will sport a 4.3-inch WQVGA touchscreen display, SiRF Star III chipset, and an in-car mounting kit, but the similarities basically end there. On the low-end, you'll find NAVTEQ maps for the 48 contiguous United States, QuickSpell, 1.6 million POIs, and a rechargeable battery with around three hours of juice. The 4040 steps it up by adding more detailed map coverage, 4.5 million POIs, text-to-speech / Bluetooth capabilities, and by playing nice with the real-time traffic add-on service. The flagship unit boasts all the capabilities of its lesser siblings, but also adds traffic functions right out of the box as well as voice recognition software. The Maestro 4000 / 4040 are each slated to land in "early April" for $449.99 / $599.99, respectively, while the high-end 4050 will demand a somewhat steep $799.99 for its niceties when it arrives in May.Read - Magellan Maestro 4000Read - Magellan Maestro 4040Read - Magellan Maestro 4050[Via GPSGazette] Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93486827/</address><date>2007-02-20T20:38:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_82"><title>AMD's new consumer flagship proc, the X2 6000+</title><summary>Filed under: Desktops
The 90nm Athlon 64 X2 processor line looks close to its last breath with the X2 6000+, a 3GHz monstrosity designed as a consumer equivalent to the FX-74. The 6000+ is limited to single processor systems, none of those quad-core frivolities the FX-74 is known to partake in, but the chip can still suck down a maximum of 125 watts, and carries 1MB of L2 cache per core. Where the 6000+ processor really departs from its enthusiast sibling is the $464 pricetag, less than half the cost of a FX-74. The chip is a few months late -- it was slated for Q4 2006 originally -- and will be followed by an 89 watt version in the third quarter of this year, along with a slightly less beefy 5800+ edition, but then its quitsville for AMD's 90nm creations. 65nm here we come! Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93476480/</address><date>2007-02-20T20:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_83"><title>ACCS GRAViTONUS gives quadriplegics tongue-controlled computer interface</title><summary>Filed under: Desktops, Misc. Gadgets
While other forms of alternative computing are certainly available, yet another group of researchers are touting their own rendition as a radical new way for quadriplegics to engage in computerized learning and entertainment. Dubbed the Alternative Computer Control System (ACCS) GRAViTONUS, the proposed hands-free system would enable folks who have suffered spinal cord injuries or other forms of paralysis to dictate basic computer functions entirely with their tongue. The prototype looks to be quite non-invasive, and when worn around one's head, can enable users to mouse around and navigate within applications by way of a precise tongue-controllable interface. Interestingly, it's even stated that the device won't hinder one's ability to drink, speak, or breathe, but we assume you'd have to give the mouthpiece a good washing after every use to avoid bacterial buildup. Nevertheless, the ACCS GRAViTONUS backers are now scouting VCs who'd like to get this creation to market, so if you've been looking for something intriguing to get wrapped up in, give these blokes a ring. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93458983/</address><date>2007-02-20T19:38:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_84"><title>Hello Kitty embraces warming blankets, gets fired up via USB</title><summary>Filed under: Misc. Gadgets
If you think we were baffled after seeing Hello Kitty USB foot warmers, you probably can't imagine the speechlessness we all feel when seeing the USB-powered lap warmer. Considering that anyone who would actually toss out their hard-earned dollars on feline feet heaters would likely not have the will power to resist this mat, it's fairly to say to say that this is a must-have for hardcore fans braving the tail end of winter. No word on just how large this thing is, nor if poses any eruption capabilities like one of its siblings (clones?), but judging by the mat-to-USB-connector ratio, this kitty ought to warmly cover a litter or two at least. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93453293/</address><date>2007-02-20T19:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_85"><title>Graffiti Research Lab's L.A.S.E.R. Tag</title><summary>Filed under: Displays
   Lessee here, we've got lasers, creative input devices, a "stick it to The Man" aesthetic and a Mooninite -- sounds like a successful night of hacking to us. Graffiti Research Lab and friends hacked together a high powered projector with some computer components and a camera to track the writings of a 60mW Green Laser on the side of a building in Rotterdam and project it as blue graffiti. The resulting art looks surprisingly good, and the perpetrators were kind enough to document the event, along with providing instructions for doing up your own version. It's hard to describe, so we recommend peeping the video after the break, or the better quality vids and pics over at the read link.[Thanks, Teferri]Continue reading Graffiti Research Lab's L.A.S.E.R. Tag Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93438390/</address><date>2007-02-20T18:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_86"><title>Australia to phase out incandescent bulbs by 2010</title><summary>Filed under: HouseholdWhile some US cities like Raleigh are already planning steps to cut back on energy wastes by converting to more efficient lighting systems, it looks like the entire continent of Australia could be following suit. Claiming to be the "world's first" national government to phase out incandescent light bulbs in favor of the more "fuel-efficient, compact fluorescent bulb," environment minister Malcolm Turnbull is hoping to "cut Australia's greenhouse gas emissions by four million metric tonnes a year by 2015." Citing the "climate changes" the world is facing as a "global challenge," Turnbell also urged other nations to follow suit in making a difference, but didn't exactly open up his personal wallet to stock our households with those uber-pricey bulbs. Interestingly, some environmentalists feel that the bulk of greenhouse gas emissions come from government and business-related activities, which should presumably take priority over swapping out a country's light bulbs. Still, we've got no complaints with hooking homes up with LED / fluorescent options to help Mother Earth, but shouldn't Australia (and America, too) ink its name on the Kyoto Protocol before getting all high and mighty about saving the planet? Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93432534/</address><date>2007-02-20T18:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_87"><title>Palm makes Treo 700wx official for Verizon</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, Handhelds
Palm and Verizon have made official today what we've known now for a while (as have Sprint and Alltel): 32MB of RAM in a Windows Mobile 5 device just doesn't really cut it. The Treo 700wx rights the 700w's wrongs with an extra 32MB of memory for a grand total of 64MB; otherwise, though, the device is all but identical to its older sibling, with Windows Mobile 6 sadly nowhere in sight. Get it now while it's hot at Verizon stores or online for a stiff $399 on 2-year contract after $100 rebate. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93414274/</address><date>2007-02-20T17:40:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_88"><title>Powered bumpers defend your smart car when all else fails</title><summary>Filed under: Robots, Transportation
Smart cars are all well and good until you start to think of the horrible consequences if something should go wrong. Honestly, we're willing to take that risk just for the rewards of cruising along in a robotic car "platoon": saving gas, skipping traffic and perhaps getting in a bit of Gears of War while we're at it. Luckily, more judicious minds than ours are hard at work at the problem, and just might've discovered a way to keep smart car-filled roads from becoming riddled with the bodies of overly-optimistic bloggers. Alasdair Renfrew of Manchester University, UK, along with a couple of colleagues, has devised an extendable fender that can keep you safe and humming along the freeway, even when traditional wireless communications fail. The smart cars will traditionally be communicating with each other and roadside beacons wirelessly, and if one of those elements breaks down, the cars bust out powered bumpers to feel the car in front and navigate accordingly. That way, as long as the front car of a pack keeps to the speed limit and in its lane, the group should be fine -- and your Xbox session needn't be interrupted. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93410533/</address><date>2007-02-20T17:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_89"><title>GoogleFi gives 360 addicts Xbox Live on the go</title><summary>Filed under: Gaming, Transportation, Wireless
   Obviously, quite a few possibilities open up when your whole town is wired for WiFi, but we can't say we really pegged drive-by 360 play as one of them. Mountain View, CA residents Brandon Wirtz and Jake Ludington fixed up Brandon's Jeep with 23-inch Samsung LCD and an Xbox connected to Google WiFi via Jake's laptop. The total cost of wire-free 360 action is about $4000 if starting from scratch, but isn't that a small price to pay for the freedom to frag?[Via BBC News] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93394047/</address><date>2007-02-20T16:38:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_90"><title>Cingular's BlackBerry 8800 unboxed</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones
He got us those original BlackBerry 8800 shots, so we're guessing these unboxing pics of the phone here were no sweat for Boy Genius. We still can't claim to be crazy about the device, which launched last week, but we're sure plenty of suits will be glad to replace their aging CrackBerries with this fancy new QWERTY version. As a side note -- could Cingular's boxes be any more boring? Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93388948/</address><date>2007-02-20T16:08:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_91"><title>Blair announces Iraq troops cut</title><summary>Tony Blair says he hopes to cut the number of UK troops in Iraq from 7,100 to 5,000 within months.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/uk_politics/6380933.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T13:15:15</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_92"><title>Tehran dismisses threat of force</title><summary>Iran's top nuclear negotiator dismisses threats of force against it, as the UN prepares to make a crucial report.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6380879.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T02:38:26</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_93"><title>Zimbabwe's police ban protests</title><summary>Zimbabwe police ban protests as Robert Mugabe marks his 83rd birthday by vowing to stay on as president.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6382405.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T11:35:20</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_94"><title>S Asia rivals sign nuclear pact</title><summary>India and Pakistan sign an agreement to reduce the risk of accidental nuclear conflict in the region.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6381261.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T11:54:32</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_95"><title>Iraq PM sacks 'rape case' critic</title><summary>Iraq's prime minister moves to put an end to disquiet about an alleged rape of a Sunni women by police.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6382119.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T13:01:17</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_96"><title>Maoists walk out of Nepal camp</title><summary>Hundreds of former Maoist rebels walk out of a holding camp in Nepal, complaining of poor conditions.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6382093.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T12:16:21</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_97"><title>Philippines army is 'in denial'</title><summary>A UN envoy says the Philippines army is in "almost total denial" about a wave of extra-judicial killings.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/asia-pacific/6381291.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T05:15:15</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_98"><title>Stars raise $1.3m for Obama</title><summary>Celebrities donate $1.3m to Democrat Barack Obama's presidential campaign at a lavish Beverly Hills fund-raiser.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6381375.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T07:55:03</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_99"><title>Britney Spears 'back into rehab'</title><summary>Pop star Britney Spears is back in rehab, days after shaving her head, US media reports say.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/entertainment/6380827.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T09:02:53</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_100"><title>Football: Lille 0-1 Man Utd</title><summary>Ryan Giggs' controversial late winner for Man Utd almost sparks a Champions League walk-out by Lille.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/sport1/hi/football/europe/6371329.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T21:38:44</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_101"><title>UN backs peace force for Somalia</title><summary>The UN Security Council approves the deployment of an African peacekeeping force to tackle unrest in Somalia.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6381189.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T08:39:08</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_102"><title>Big Anglo American profits jump</title><summary>Mining giant Anglo American is to return $3bn to shareholders after reporting a 46% rise in annual profits.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/business/6381739.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T09:36:52</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_103"><title>US probes troops' neglect claims</title><summary>The US says it is reviewing the way its wounded soldiers are cared for at hospitals, after critical media reports.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6381453.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T09:17:06</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_104"><title>No end to deadly Bolivian floods</title><summary>Up to 340,000 people have been affected by continuing flooding in Bolivia, which has left 35 people dead.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6380331.stm</address><date>2007-02-20T18:25:36</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_105"><title>Japan ups interest rates to 0.5%</title><summary>Japan's central bank shows signs of confidence in the country's economy, raising interest rates to 0.5%.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/business/6381335.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T08:07:26</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_106"><title>Prison demand for Poso suspects</title><summary>Indonesia prosecutors seek 20 year jail terms for three men accused of beheading Christian schoolgirls.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/asia-pacific/6381511.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T08:40:06</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_107"><title>Denmark to pull troops from Iraq</title><summary>Denmark will withdraw its troops from Iraq by August, Danish Prime Minister Anders Fogh Rasmussen says.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6382675.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T13:07:30</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_108"><title>Leaders discuss UN's Kosovo plan</title><summary>Serbian and ethnic Albanian leaders are holding final talks in Vienna on the UN plan for Kosovo's future.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/europe/6380565.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T11:48:45</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_109"><title>Iran 'swiftly seeks nuclear goal'</title><summary>Iran's president says he wants nuclear power as soon as possible, as critics in Iran urge him to accept UN demands.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6381477.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T12:10:51</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_110"><title>Militant dies in Israeli ambush</title><summary>Israeli undercover agents kill a commander of the militant Islamic Jihad group in the northern West Bank.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6381653.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T08:49:42</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_111"><title>India eyes Scotch takeover</title><summary>An Indian businessman is set to complete a deal to buy Scottish whisky firm Whyte and Mackay for ?550m.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/business/6381339.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T13:04:47</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_112"><title>India boat capsize bodies found</title><summary>Rescue workers recover bodies of 15 children and three men from a school trip boat accident in India.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6381289.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T04:57:46</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_113"><title>Blair announces Iraq troops cut</title><summary>Tony Blair says he hopes to cut the number of UK troops in Iraq from 7,100 to 5,000 within months.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/uk_politics/6380933.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T13:44:46</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_114"><title>Fear as cyclone nears Mozambique</title><summary>Mozambique is on the highest level of alert as a cyclone with winds of up to 175km/h approaches.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/africa/6383675.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T17:06:58</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_115"><title>Italian PM faces coalition crisis</title><summary>Italy's Romano Prodi calls a special cabinet session after his fragile coalition loses a key foreign policy vote.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/6383051.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T17:22:45</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_116"><title>Fujifilm's FinePix S5700</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
  Another hot off the pre-PMA presses, Fujifilm's got their new FinePix S5600 followup ready to go, the S5700. It's got a 10x zoom, 7.1 megapixel sensor, 2.5-inch display, 1600 ISO setting, image stabilization, 27MB internal memory, and, you're not going to believe this, xD and SD support. Unfortunately it uses four AA cells instead of a nice Li-ion battery. No price just yet, but the black model lands (somewhere) at the end of March, with the silver following in April.Gallery: Fujifilm's FinePix S5700 Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94150403/</address><date>2007-02-22T06:14:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_117"><title>Fujifilm's FinePix A820 and A900 for consumers</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
   Just like Canon's new PMA-bound A Series cameras, Fujifilm's new A820 and A900 cameras don't really break a lot of new ground, but there sure is a lot more megapixel bang-for-buck going on here. For $180 and $200, respectively, the A820 brings 8 megapixels and the A900 goes for 9, while both camera have 4x zooms and 2.5-inch LCDs. Unfortunately, there doesn't seem to be any form of optical image stabilisation here, nor any of those much-hyped Face Recognition AF/AE features we've been seeing in other PMA offerings, but if all you're looking for is pixels and lots of 'em, you can't go far wrong with this pair of FinePix, which will be hitting shelves in March. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94137650/</address><date>2007-02-22T05:46:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_118"><title>Canon's new PowerShot A570 and A560</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
   Canon sure likes to yuk it up with the "A Series" puns. "A" for affordable, for the AA batteries you can stick in these things, for the "A" Team the cameras represent -- it's a real riot. Luckily, "affordable" doesn't have to mean "boring" anymore, and these two PowerShots include fancy 4x zooms, 7.1 megapixel CCDs, 2.5-inch LCDs and that DIGIC III processor for speedier operation, along with 1600 ISO and Face Detection. Sound familiar? You can have it all for a few more bucks, 1x less zoom and quite a bit more pocketability in the Digital ELPH series. What the A570 adds that the A560 and those ELPH cousins lack is optical image stabilisation. You can pick one up for $280, or if you don't mind the blur, grab an A560 for $230. Both will be out in March.Gallery: Canon's new PowerShot A570 and A560 Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94115873/</address><date>2007-02-22T04:43:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_119"><title>Canon's compact PowerShot TX1 captures 7.1 megapixel stills and HD video</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
   Watch out, Sanyo, because your diminutive HD2 camcorder is about to face some very daunting competition from Canon. Like the recently announced Sanyo, the PowerShot TX1 packs a 7.1 megapixel CCD into a tiny little package capable of capturing 720p HD video as well -- but unlike the $700 HD2, Canon is hanging just a $500 pricetag on this model. Besides its one-two punch of high resolution stills and videos, this device offers a 10x optical zoom (with an optically-stabilized lens), a 115,000 pixel LCD, and ISO settings ranging from 80 to 1600. You're also getting the latest Digic image processor, advanced face detection and red eye reduction, Vista-compatibility, 14 shooting modes, and a so-called "Intelligent Orientation Sensor" to keep the display looking right no matter how you're holding the cam. No word so far on a release date, but with all this functionality at a very attractive price, you can probably expect the TX1 to fly off shelves when it finally makes its debut.Gallery: Canon's compact PowerShot TX1 captures 7.1 megapixel stills and HD video Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94113961/</address><date>2007-02-22T04:25:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_120"><title>Canon debuts SD750 and SD1000 Digital ELPH cameras</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
   Two new compact and fashionable PowerShot Digital ELPHs from big C, the SD750 and SD1000. Canon seems to be mostly focused on the looks here: we've never seen a growed-up digicam manufacturer be so proud of "Dynamic Dual-Tone Elegance," but there's decent stuff under the hood. Like most of the PMA-bound cameras we've spotted, these include Face Detection-based auto focus, auto exposure and red-eye correction. There's also the DIGIC III Image processor, and ISO as high as 1600, but everybody comes for the basics: 3x zoom, 7.1 megapixel CCD and a 2.5-inch LCD in each shooter. The $300 SD750 gets a bit fancy on form factor, but manages to be a mere 0.75-inches thick, while the 4.5 ounce SD1000 keeps the the classic ELPH look and also retails for $300. Both should be out in March, and include 32MB SD cards for good luck, though no mention is made of SDHC. Remember, it's fashion first for this line.Gallery: Canon debuts SD750 and SD1000 Digital ELPH cameras Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94113962/</address><date>2007-02-22T04:23:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_121"><title>Canon's EOS-1D Mark III DSLR with live LCD</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
  Canon's latest pro DSLR is officially here as of tonight: welcome the EOS-1D Mark III. This 10.1 megapixel shooter can fire 10fps in bursts of up to 110 large JPEGs or 30 RAW files with is dual DIGIC III processor. It also features a really friggin light sensitive APS-H size 28.1 x 18.7mm CMOS sensor with ISO modes up to 3200 (it's also got a "highly usable" just-in-case 6400 mode sure to kill image quality), but the real winner here is the 3-inch live LCD (with 5 and 10x magnification for locking that zoom). There's also a new WFT- E2A Wireless File Transmitter option for dumping to external storage and even GPS geotagging, the OSK-E3 Original Data Security Kit for file encryption and verification (if your images are just that valuable), the Speedlite 580EX II flash, and EF 16-35mm f/2.8L II USM lens. We don't yet have word on price or release date, but you know what they say about having to ask.Gallery: Canon's EOS-1D Mark III DSLR with live LCD Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94110286/</address><date>2007-02-22T04:16:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_122"><title>S1Digital's impressive new lineup of Media Centers</title><summary>Filed under: Home Entertainment, Media PCsMedia Centers are so in now and that you have to really do something to make your black box stand out, and S1Digital's new lineup of media centers and servers does just that. Actually there are two series, the ProLine for professional installers and home automation companies and the Home Series for the rest of us. The Home Series includes the Platinum, Gold and Mighty editions, all running Core 2 Duo processors and Vista Home Premium. The Mighty is the size of a book and includes built in WiFi and DVD burner. Up next is the Gold, which is a more traditional size and adds up to 1TB of storage, HDMI, 2 ATSC and 2 NTSC tuners (sorry no CableCARD here), 7.1 audio and Viiv. The Platinum tops the Home Series, adding a quiet design an internal scaler and optional HD DVD or Blu-ray drive. But they don't stop there and are trying to join Niveus in the high end market with the ProLine Series, which of course does everything the Home series does, but with Vista Ultimate, rack mountable, a silent design and two-way control for all your favorite home automation systems like Crestron and AMX. As impressive as this lineup is, we are once again left wonder, where are the CableCARDs?Read: S1Digital Introduces the Home Series Line of Media CentersRead: S1Digital Sets a New Reference Standard with ProLine Series Media Centers Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94110287/</address><date>2007-02-22T04:04:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_123"><title>Apple and Cisco settle! iPhone name to be used by both</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones


Here's one we didn't exactly see coming (at least not like this): Apple and Cisco have settled that "silly" lawsuit, with Apple agreeing to guarantee the exploration of "interoperability in the areas of security, and consumer and enterprise communications" according to the WSJ. We don't know exactly what that means, but it doesn't sound fantastic for Jobs, who we're sure wanted to have exclusivity over the name without cutting a partnership with Cisco, and didn't want to have to pay a red cent for it. But this does sound a lot like what Cisco wanted initially from Apple, and might possibly wind up in some kind of SIP / VoIP solution that allows iPhones and iPhones to communicate. Apparently both will make use of the trademark in the market (i.e. Apple's and Cisco's iPhones will both continue to be iPhones), and all's well that ends non-litigious.[Thanks, Nick and Jay] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94075975/</address><date>2007-02-22T02:42:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_124"><title>Nintendo Wii beats up on the competition in power savings</title><summary>Filed under: Gaming, Home Entertainment
So, the graphics might just be warmed over GameCube fare, but the Wii sure does take those wimpy specs and runs with 'em. A new showdown between the big three home consoles and a mid-range PC doesn't compare games or GPUs, but rather power consumption, and the Wii wins by a landslide. The watts don't just bleed during gameplay, DVD playback seems to require immense effort from the 360 and PS3, and even the consoles in "idle" mode consume about ten times the watts of the Wii. Of course, the consoles consume a minimal amount of power in standby, which is substantially more when the Wii's Connect24 service is on, but not quite a deal breaker, just about a $1 a month of power. So if you're looking to shave a few bucks off your power bill or do your treehuggin' duty to the environment, it looks like the choice is fairly obvious -- though you'll naturally have to look elsewhere than the Wii to get your video playback kicks.[Via Joystiq] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94066659/</address><date>2007-02-22T02:09:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_125"><title>Frenzy   Rumble transforming headphones: lamer it sounds</title><summary>Filed under: Misc. Gadgets, Portable Audio
You know, a Transformers movie was really its own reward, but all these transforming gadgets -- movie related and no -- are really making it all the more exciting, especially when we're talking completely superfluous fluff. Take these new Frenzy   Rumble Earphones, for example. There's no reason you'd want 'em on your head, and there's no way they push out an adequate volume for desktop use when in that transformed state. A perfect blend of uselessness and inconvenience. You can get yours in July for about $37.[Thanks, Aaron D] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94046982/</address><date>2007-02-22T01:14:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_126"><title>Bill Gates clamps down on daughter's internet time</title><summary>Filed under: Desktops, Laptops, Tablet PCsSure, we've seen individuals getting their hand slapped (or worse) for browsing the internet a bit too often, but you'd assume that having a dad who envisioned the Redmond powerhouse and pays the bills by way of computing would be the perfect father figure for the computer-addicted. Apparently, that's not exactly so, as a recent Reuters report tells of Bill Gates himself clamping down on his 10-year old daughter's internet and gaming time. According to Bill, his oldest gal wasn't even into the 'net until this school year, where tablet PCs became a necessary tool, but now that she's found access to a never-ending supply of information, her habits have suddenly changed. She latched onto Viva Pi ata, purportedly playing for "two to three hours per day," after which her health started deteriorating and her chore accomplishments plummeted. Although we mention those last bits in jest, Mr. Gates slapped down a "45-minutes per day" law for non-school related computing tasks on the weekdays, and added just 15 minutes for weekends, probably garnering quite the evil eye and stirring up early thoughts of rebellion in his youngster. Seriously Bill, if you're that worried about daddy's little girl stumbling upon some form of cyber predator, there's always the parent-approved IM-Me, but throwing time restrictions on your own products is just a tad illogical, no?[Via BloggingStocks, thanks Randall] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94027868/</address><date>2007-02-22T00:19:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_127"><title>Pentax busts out Hasselbladian 31.6 megapixel 645 Digital</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
   Pentax has apparently tapped Kodak to provide its 31.6 megapixel KAF-31600 medium format CCD for the upcoming 645 Digital, which would seem to be the company's highest resolution digital camera to date. So far all that's known from the pre-PMA announcement is that the 645 will sport both SD and CF slots, and will ship with a specially-built 55mm lens that's also compatible with 645-series SLR film cameras. We should find out more about this behemoth in early March -- although possibly not pricing and release info -- but one thing we can say for sure is that if it's priced anything like the Hasselblad H3D-31 whose sensor it shares, expect to pay out well into five figures.[Thanks, David N.] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94009335/</address><date>2007-02-21T23:24:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_128"><title>Pentax pops out the Optio W30 and A30</title><summary>Filed under: Digital Cameras
There's some heated competition already for our PMA eyeballs, and Pentax sure wants a slice. They don't have anything terribly outstanding on the consumer end, but these W30 and A30 Optio shooters still do pretty well for themselves. The A30 (pictured) takes a pretty traditional approach to the compact genre, boosting the megapixels to 10 and offering up 2.5-inches of LCD. There's also ISO 3200 and some fancy gyro-based shake reduction, along with face recognition auto focus and auto exposure, all in a pretty dang compact SDHC-munching body. The W30 steps it back a bit, with a 7.1 megapixel CCD and mere digital shake reduction, but the rest of the specs are there, along with a waterproof and dustproof housing that can handle being up to three meters under water for two hours. No word on price or availability for either camera, but we're sure we'll be finding out soon enough. Peep the W30 after the break.[Thanks, David N]Read - Optio A30Read - Optio W30Continue reading Pentax pops out the Optio W30 and A30 Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/94000890/</address><date>2007-02-21T23:09:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_129"><title>Xbox 360 Wireless Receiver for Windows now available</title><summary>Filed under: Desktops, Gaming, Peripherals, Wireless
It sure took its own sweet time to make it to market -- we first saw this thing at E3 in 2006 -- but the Xbox 360 Wireless Receiver for Windows is finally available for purchase. The adapter lets you use your standard wireless 360 peripherals, such as the Xbox 360 Wireless Controller and Wireless Headset, with your Windows PC. That means Windows users, which have been enjoying the fruits of a USB 360 controller since before the console launched, can finally get in on some wireless action, and it'll only cost them $20 for the privilege. It also means that much more fun for upcoming Games for Windows titles such as Shadowrun, UNO and Halo 2, along with generic game controls and VoIP functionality. Microsoft is also releasing a $60 package which includes a receiver and a wireless controller. Both items should be available at retail now. Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93985665/</address><date>2007-02-21T22:24:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_130"><title>Engadget Podcast 100 - 02.21.2007</title><summary>Engadget Podcast 100</summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93966098/</address><date>2007-02-21T21:49:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_131"><title>Switched On: What of the Wii-buked?</title><summary>Filed under: Features, Gaming  
Each week Ross Rubin contributes Switched On, a column about technology, multimedia, and digital entertainment:

Nintendo has been on an Apple-like hit parade since the disappointing market performance of the GameCube. The DS and DS Lite handily staved off highly touted competition from Sony. The PSP may have appealed to a different, if for now narrower, demographic, but units are units, and there's no escaping them when you're marketing a platform.
The launch of the Wii has been nothing but magic mushrooms from the hype around the controller to the E3 reception to late-night Wii Tennis face-offs between Conan and Serena Williams. Check out this apologetic fan comment on Amazon's product page: "Graphics might not be high definition, but it looks very close to the Xbox 360 and PS3 when not running in HD mode. And definitively better than the original Xbox and PS2." Better than the Xbox and PS2, eh? That's setting the sensor bar pretty low for a system that shipped six years after the PS2. 
Yet, it's no suprise that the Wii has been highly sought. I thought it was the best consumer technology product of 2006. The Nintendo team has executed almost flawlessly, but the company has brushed aside criticisms regarding product shortages without so much as a flick from a Wiimote. Commenting earlier this month on the mayhem surrounding Sony's PlayStation 3's product launch shortages, Nintendo of America vice president of marketing and corporate affairs Perrin Kaplan noted that "we didn't have anyone in line that got shot waiting for our system. So there's one sign of the different approaches between our two companies."Continue reading Switched On: What of the Wii-buked? Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93966099/</address><date>2007-02-21T21:34:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_132"><title>Sirius' and XM's merger presentation revealed</title><summary>Filed under: Portable Audio, Portable Video
   Brace yourself: corporate speak ahead. We normally aren't in for all this "cost synergies" and "roadmap" hogwash that all the suits seem to get so hot for, but when it comes to a merger of two cutthroat competitors like this, we couldn't help but take a peek. Other than the technology improvements we mentioned, there isn't much talk about consumer benefits in here, and there's absolutely no mention of creating some sort of single satellite radio provider, just the power of combined resources. Most of the talk is directed at shareholders and those "synergies" that help out the bottom line -- to the tune of an estimated $3-7 billion in savings, though a $4 billion "flex" does seem to cast a bit of doubt on those numbers. The rest of the slides deal with plans for getting regulatory approval, which basically amount to arguing the case of intense competition from radio, iPods and other emerging wireless standards (see above). That said, XM and Sirius seem quite confident of success on the regulatory end of things, and look to have put a quite a bit of thought into it. Pending approval from the feds, along with respective shareholder go-ahead, XM and Sirius plan on sealing the deal by the end of 2007.Gallery: Sirius and XM's merger presentation revealed Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93959647/</address><date>2007-02-21T21:12:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_133"><title>Art Lebedev intros Verbarius electronic clock</title><summary>Filed under: Misc. GadgetsArt Lebedev may be best known these days for its various display-ridden peripherals, and the delays and uncertainty surrounding each, but the prolific design firm's got plenty more on its plate, to which it's now added the Verbarius electronic clock. As you can see above, the clock does away with the usual time-telling tools in favor of spelling things out, in five different languages no less. What's more, it changes up its verbiage each time you ask it the time, displaying variations like "forty-five minutes past four," "fifteen minutes to five," "four forty-five", and "a quarter to five." This being Lebedev, of course, they're also taking their time to build up anticipation in the device, with the clock supposedly set to only begin shipping in November. You can get your pre-orders in now, however, with a discount price of $158.25 available to those who order before September 1st, after which it'll set you back about $180. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93944802/</address><date>2007-02-21T20:44:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_134"><title>HTC "Gene" makes FCC appearance</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, Handhelds
After a fairly productive 3GSM last week showing off new Windows Mobile 6 wares in the form of the Vox and the Advantage, everyone's favorite Taiwanese Windows Mobile ODM has graced us with this here "Gene" (or at least we think that's what it's called, based on its model number, GENE100) via our usual Tipster Extraordinare, the FCC. The specs aren't really enough to knock our socks off -- data tops out with quadband EDGE, the cam is a simple 2 megapixel unit, plus the usual Bluetooth 2.0, 128MB of ROM, 64MB of RAM, and QVGA display atop a 201MHz TI OMAP850 -- but at this point, we're still happy to get whatever new Professional hardware we can get. Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93941965/</address><date>2007-02-21T20:24:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_135"><title>Helio's Pantech PN-810 QWERTY device pops up in FCC</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, Handhelds
And here it is, Helio's coup de gr ce. The QWERTY handset we'd heard Helio was cookin' up with Korea's Pantech actually hit the FCC some time ago, but the shots we were able to glean from the test apparatus documentation were teasers at best. Thanks to the wonders of expired confientiality agreements, that same FCC documentation now yields a bounty of goodness, including a user's manual and a full array of pictures. The so-called PN-810 gives the illusion of a dual slider, but actually employs two distinct layers to provide two completely different keypads depending on the slide direction: QWERTY in one, numeric in the other. Key features (other than the unusual form factor, of course) include a 2.1 megapixel cam, Bluetooth, and the full array of goodies that comes with Helio membership. A release date remains uncertain, but the PN-810's been chilling with the feds for some time now, so we wouldn't be terribly surprised to see it hit in the near term.Gallery: Helio's Pantech PN-810 QWERTY device pops up in FCC Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93938442/</address><date>2007-02-21T20:05:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_136"><title>ATI's R600 graphics chip hits snag</title><summary>Filed under: Desktops, GamingWe've had our eye on ATI"s new top-end R600 graphics chip for some time now, first getting a look at some impressive early benchmarks and then being taken aback by the foot-long graphics card the chips will call home (at least in some configurations). Sadly, it seems that those with money and power (as in 270W) to spare will have to wait a bit longer to slot one of the behemoths into their own PCs, with The Inquirer reporting that the R600 chips, and consequently the graphics cards based on 'em, have been delayed yet again, now pushed back to sometime in the second quarter of this year. There doesn't seem to be any word on the reason for the delay, but the news apparently came straight from ATI parent company AMD. Given what the cards are likely to cost, however, we're guessing that at least some won't be too disappointed in the delay, with the extra time allowing you to save up some more money and make some more excuses for why you're spending so much on a graphics card.[Via TG Daily] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93920986/</address><date>2007-02-21T19:32:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_137"><title>Russians congregate over internet, drink via USB shot glasses</title><summary>Filed under: Misc. Gadgets
   Considering that we've all some of us have been enjoying online chats, poker, and dating for quite some while, it's not too shocking to see the Russians utilize the power of the web to bring alcoholics and social drinkers together in inebriated harmony. Sergey Mikheev, head of e-generator, has devised a USB shot glass to allow lonely, alcohol-needing individuals to get their drink on while safely at home. While we don't consider ourselves experts in Russian culture, it's apparently not tactful to get plastered solo, and while online drinking might be stretching the rules just a bit, we're sure those vodka-lovin' internet dwellers aren't complaining. The idea is to join a group of drinkers in an online lounge, where the USB shot glass levels are shown on each person's screen; once the go-ahead is given, the folks turn up their glasses and chug it down, ideally showing an empty glass after a random smashing of keys somehow spells out congratulatory phrases. As interesting and novel as this may be, let it remind us all how "getting a life" should be taken oh-so-seriously.[Via ChipChick] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93918114/</address><date>2007-02-21T19:02:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_138"><title>Samsung's 19-inch SyncMaster 940UX LCD picks USB</title><summary>Filed under: Displays
After DisplayLink hit us up with a cordless monitor care of Wireless USB, things really can't get much simpler for connecting LCDs with PC towers, but for those not quite ready to jump into all that, Samsung is reportedly readying a USB-only monitor that'll be showcased at CeBIT. Yep, according to reports, the 19-inch SyncMaster 940UX will be axing the DVI and VGA inputs in favor of a USB 2.0 connector, which means you can finally do away with those flakey USB to VGA adapters of days past. Slated for a May release, the display should sync up with Windows XP initially, with Vista drivers (no OS X love?) to follow shortly thereafter. No other details regarding contrast ratio, resolution, or whether a 0.25-page installation manual will be included is currently available, and more importantly, we're not so sure how your CPU is going to feel about its newfangled processing duties when you plug this sucka in. Still, Samsung claims between "three and five" of these monitors can be plugged in and used at any given time based on the amount of processing requirements your applications have, but the real question is how quickly can ATI / NVIDIA can crank out a next-generation GPU with USB 2.0 outputs, eh?[Via Slashgear] Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93898699/</address><date>2007-02-21T18:32:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="1" unread="true" id="alert_139"><title>Latest BlackBerry OS confirms 8820 with WiFi</title><summary>Filed under: Cellphones, Handhelds, Wireless
  A feature notoriously missing from RIM's range, WiFi is one add-on we can pretty much all agree would make the average BlackBerry user's life noticeably better. We'd heard rumblings ahead of the 8800's release that Canada's newest handset would sport some manner of 802.11 out of the box, but alas -- the release came and went with no 2.4GHz (or 5GHz, for that matter) goodness in sight, allegedly due to technical glitches on RIM's side that the company was unwilling to delay the initial model for. No worries, though -- well, maybe a few worries if you're AT T and you're trying to push the 8800 out the door -- the WiFi-enabled 8820 looks pretty official now thanks to a cameo in RIM's latest BlackBerry OS offering. Other changes should be minimal from its predecessor; a camera still isn't in the cards, leaving shutterbugs who like their BlackBerry served QWERTY style up the same creek they are now. No word on a release, but rumblings have the device launching mid-year. Read | Permalink | Email this | CommentsBOLD MOVES: THE FUTURE OF FORD A new documentary series. Be part of the transformation as it happens in real-timeOffice Depot Featured Gadget: Xbox 360 Platinum System Packs the power to bring games to life!
 </summary><address>http://feeds.engadget.com/~r/weblogsinc/engadget/~3/93882167/</address><date>2007-02-21T18:02:00</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_140"><title>Italian crisis talks as PM quits</title><summary>Italian President Giorgio Napolitano is to begin crisis talks after the resignation of PM Romano Prodi.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/europe/6384953.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T07:09:56</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_141"><title>Iraq leader welcomes troops' exit</title><summary>The Iraqi president welcomes Tony Blair's plans to cut UK troops in Iraq from 7,100 to 5,000 within months.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/uk_politics/6384685.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T01:06:14</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_142"><title>Apple and Cisco share iPhone</title><summary>Apple and Cisco Systems agree to share the iPhone trademark, allowing both firms to use the name.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/business/6384875.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T04:52:01</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_143"><title>Indonesia ferry fire kills six</title><summary>At least seven people - two of them children - die as fire breaks out on a ferry sailing from Indonesia's capital.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/asia-pacific/6384859.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T07:29:35</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_144"><title>Clinton and Obama row erupts</title><summary>A row erupts between two leading contenders for the US Democratic Party's presidential nomination.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6384821.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T02:02:19</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_145"><title>Menchu to stand in Guatemala</title><summary>Indigenous activist and Nobel winner Rigoberta Menchu says she will run for president in Guatemala.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6384845.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T03:33:05</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_146"><title>Most-premature baby goes home</title><summary>The world's most-premature baby leaves a Miami hospital, four months after weighing in at just 280 grams.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6384621.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T22:33:54</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_147"><title>US wants tougher Iran sanctions</title><summary>Washington says it will now push for tougher sanctions against Iran over its nuclear activities.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6384725.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T23:43:08</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_148"><title>US soldier admits murdering girl</title><summary>A second US soldier admits to the gang rape and murder of a 14-year-old Iraqi girl and her family.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6384781.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T01:40:53</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_149"><title>Football: Barca 1-2 L'pool</title><summary>Craig Bellamy and John Arne Riise both score as Liverpool beat holders Barcelona in the first leg of their Champions League tie.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/sport1/hi/football/europe/6371395.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T21:37:03</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_150"><title>Football: Porto 1-1 Chelsea</title><summary>Andriy Shevchenko's goal earns Chelsea a draw, but the Blues lose John Terry to an ankle injury in Porto.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/sport1/hi/football/europe/6371399.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T21:36:15</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_151"><title>Crisis talks over Bolivian floods</title><summary>The Bolivian government is holding emergency talks over the severe flooding in much of the country.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/americas/6384267.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T20:54:40</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_152"><title>Spears 'leaves rehab after a day'</title><summary>Pop star Britney Spears has left a rehab centre after just one day for the second time, according to US reports.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/entertainment/6384081.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T18:31:01</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_153"><title>Australia may lift Afghan force</title><summary>Australia studies sending 450 more troops to Afghanistan, as US Vice-President Dick Cheney prepares to visit.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/asia-pacific/6384965.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T06:43:29</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_154"><title>Blair announces Iraq troops cut</title><summary>Tony Blair says he hopes to cut the number of UK troops in Iraq from 7,100 to 5,000 within months.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/uk_politics/6380933.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T18:15:55</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_155"><title>India ban on Iran nuclear exports</title><summary>Indian officials say exports to Iran that could be used in the country's nuclear programme have been banned.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6384919.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T05:52:36</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_156"><title>Quartet warning to Palestinians</title><summary>The Quartet of Mid-East peace negotiators says the new Palestinian government must recognise Israel.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/6384189.stm</address><date>2007-02-21T20:30:30</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_157"><title>Three 'detained' over train blast</title><summary>Police in India say they are holding three people after Sunday's bomb attack on a train to Pakistan.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6384867.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T05:20:31</date></alert><alert sourceid="0" unread="true" id="alert_158"><title>India state airlines set to merge</title><summary>Air India and Indian, India's two main state-owned airlines, are to merge to compete with private rivals.</summary><address>http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/rss/-/1/hi/world/south_asia/6384881.stm</address><date>2007-02-22T05:11:16</date></alert></alerts>
